- Okay, so
Được rồi,
I kind of want us to try something a little bit different,
cô muốn chúng ta thử cái gì đó khác biệt một chút
to, sort of, wrap this up.
để kết thúc phần này.
I was thinking you guys seems like you&#39;re really comfortable
Cô nghĩ rằng các con dường như thực sự thoải mái &#39
in terms of analyzing the text for bias
khi phân tích văn bản để tìm hiểu về thành kiến
and then doing a little bit compare, contrast work.
và sau đó thực hiện việc so sánh, đối chiếu.
I was thinking it could be sort of cool if you take
Cô nghĩ sẽ rất tuyệt
this to your groups
nếu các con mang những thứ này về nhóm của mình
and then you, sort of, teach them what we tried.
rồi sau đó dạy các bạn những gì mà cô trò mình đã thử.
D&#39;you think you could do that?
Các con nghĩ mình có thể làm được không? &#39
So, what would you say if you were gonna teach someone
Vậy các con sẽ nói gì nếu các con dạy một bạn nào đó
what we just did?
về những gì chúng ta vừa mới làm?
What would you, sort of, highlight for them?
Các con sẽ đánh dấu những gì cho các bạn thấy?
- Look at the little print. - Look at,
Có thể là,
maybe look at the fine print.
"Hãy nhìn vào "
- Okay, and what did we do when we started?
Ok. Vậy chúng ta đã làm gì khi bắt đầu?
- Pay attention to details.
Hãy chú ý đến những chi tiết.
- We paid attention to details.
Chúng ta đã chú ý đến những chi tiết.
We also checked out - We looked at the source.
Chúng ta cũng đã kiểm tra- Chúng ta nhìn vào nguồn trích dẫn.
- the source, right? - Yeah.
nguồn trích dẫn, đúng không nào?
- So, - And kinda like,
và, kiểu như
find their purpose.
tìm ra mục đích của họ.
- Yeah, exactly.
Đúng rồi, chính xác.
We&#39;re thinking like, - What they wanna do.
Chúng ta sẽ nghĩ là,  &#39; họ muốn làm gì
- what do they want us to do as readers, right?
"Họ muốn chúng ta làm gì với tư cách là dộc giả, đúng không?
So, Noel and Ishan, can I have you share what we did
Noel và Ishan, cô muốn các em chia sẻ những gì chúng ta đã học
with Tigashi and Lichia?
với Tigashi và Lichia được không?
And then Amalia and Charlie, do you feel like you can talk
Còn Amalia và Charlie, các em có nghĩ
to Charlie and Isabelle?
mình có thể nói chuyện với Charlie và Isabelle được không?
And just kinda keep it kinda quiet and whisper,
Hãy giữ yên lặng và chỉ thì thầm thôi nhé,
so that everyone else can keep working,
để các bạn khác có thể tiếp tục làm việc.
but take these with you, so you can try it all out.
Nhưng hãy mang những tờ giấy này để sử dụng.
- [Woman] For the sample.
[] Ví dụ
- And now needing powder, at 60 calories, not 160
Giờ chúng ta cần bột, 60 calo, không phải 160
and 13 grams of sugar.
và 13 gam đường.
And so, if Roland has - Maybe that&#39;s because
Nếu Roland có- Có thể là vì &#39
- Fine.
Được rồi.
- Saying this is how much that is.
- Saying this is how much that is.
- These two aren&#39;t leading,
- These two aren&#39;t leading,
maybe it&#39;s just their chocolate milk?
có thể chỉ là sữa sô- cô- la
- I know, these two aren&#39;t leading.
Tớ biết, hai cái này
- Right. - So, they&#39;re saying,
Đúng vậy-
They&#39;re either picking the syrup, or they--
Hoặc là họ chọn si- rô, hoặc là
- They should really help-- - They&#39;re either
- They should really help-- - They&#39;re either
picking the syrup and the powder with the most sugar,
picking the syrup and the powder with the most sugar,
out of all them are better-- - Right, &#39;cause that&#39;s
out of all them are better-- - Right, &#39;cause that&#39;s
what people would want. - And then
what people would want. - And then
the fine print says, &quot;Leading syrup has 100 calories.&quot;
the fine print says, &quot;Leading syrup has 100 calories.&quot;
Which is less than their chocolate milk
Which is less than their chocolate milk
and they&#39;ll go to tiny print.
and they&#39;ll go to tiny print.
So, it&#39;s like - Stupid,
So, it&#39;s like - Stupid,
why would they do that?
why would they do that?
- Because you can&#39;t usually,
- Because you can&#39;t usually,
do you ever read the fine print?
do you ever read the fine print?
- Yeah, sometimes.
- Yeah, sometimes.
- [Girl With Glasses] And they would&#39;ve just lied
- [Girl With Glasses] And they would&#39;ve just lied
to the customer.
to the customer.
- Okay, I don&#39;t usually, unless it&#39;s like this,
- Okay, I don&#39;t usually, unless it&#39;s like this,
but, you know, there&#39;s a-- - Interesting.
but, you know, there&#39;s a-- - Interesting.
- Didn&#39;t we also?
- Didn&#39;t we also?